Guide to the Henri Chopin Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Material, 1957-2007; Series VII; 15.62; (46 boxes) + 3 objects
  - Sound Recordings
    - Reel-to-reel tapes
      - Orton, Richard. "Kiss" (PT 211), 1969; 1; 00:06:46 (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889205)
        A note from Richard Orton of Lyons Concert Hall, University of York, is included with the reel. It reads: Dear Henri - A kiss for you. Richard; stero 2-track, reduction from 4-track, 7 1/2 ips; realised at the York University Studio for Electronic Music
      - Peto / v.d. Kooy / Doesburg. "Judy" (PT 201), undated; 1; 00:06:48 (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889213)
        19 cm
      - Rühm, Gerhard. "Auditive Texte" (PT 190), 1971-1975; 1; 00:18:09 (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889221)
      - Rühm, Gerhard. "Spricht über auditive Poesie" (PT 203), 1977; 1; 00:05:21 (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889239)
      - Ruppenthal, Stephen. "Two text-sound compositions" (PT 56), 1975-1978; 1; 00:12:04 (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889858)
        A note on the cover, dated 1978-11-16, reads: For Henri, from Stephen with the greatest admiration for your work. Bravo! Other information on formatting includes: stereo, 2-track, 7 1/2 ips (19 cm).
        Compositions
        Kakao-Poetic Lippudenies of the Ungumptious (1975)
        Improvisation for Processed Voice & Electronics (1978)
      - Sarenco. "English course" (PT 143), 1976-1978; 1; 00:18:29; The program is recorded at a very low level. (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889247)
        Improvvisazione Vocale Collettiva: Balon Baleur (1978), Calaone-Baone (PD), Italy; 19 cm/sec, 2 piste, stereo
      - Unknown. "Schwitters Sonate in Urlauten" (PT 97), undated; 1; 00:05:46; Pockets of silence from 03:44-04:17 and 04:30-05:36 recorded on the tape. Static can be heard in the audio. The program is distorted at times. (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889254)
      - Settles, Roberta. "Divertissements" (PT 119), 1973; 1; 00:13:40 (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889841)
        Swedish Radio/Fylking En; text - Sound Festival; 7'00" - 38
      - Seuphor, Michel. Untitled (PT 162), undated; 1; 00:19:22 (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889874)
      - Texier, Marc. "Souffles" (PT 179), 1; 00:02:56 (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889866)
        marc texies; 19 cm/s, durée 4'
      - Toby. "Father of our thoughts" (PT 55), 2007; 1; 00:09:32 (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889890)
        TOBY, Second generation in 1/2 track @ 7 1/2 IPS
      - Trio d'Eté. Untitled (PT 14), 1979 July 31; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104507174)
      - Tristan, F. "Mystère IV" (PT 195), undated; 1; 00:03:35; The program is recorded at a high level and is distorted at times. (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889262)
      - Unknown (PT 209), undated; 1; 00:06:14 (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889270)
        2° version
      - Unclear (either Chopin or Da Silva) (PT 134), undated; 1; 01:18:31; The program is distorted at times. (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889288)
        piste 1; WB faire le ler avec 4 p.m. pour 73; 2° sans pm pour 72; Le discours des ministres 38/[?]
      - Unknown. "Silencio" (PT 171), undated; 1; 01:32:38; The program is distorted at times. A warble can be heard on the tape from 25:00 to 31:20 at times. (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889296)
      - Unknown. "Les quatre dernières et émissions de H.C." (PT 98), undated; 1; 00:40:01; Static can be heard on the reel. A high amount of hiss can be heard from 20:31 to the end of the reel. (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889304)
        Dêbut.
      - Unknown (PT 191), undated; 1; 00:35:10; Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889320)
      - Unknown. "Vocabularia / Pesciaria" (PT 194), 1977; 1; 00:10:25 (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889338)
        Italy
      - Unknown. "Le palaois enchanté" (PT 31), undated; 1; 00:41:08 (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889882)
      - Unknown. "Tellurgie" (PT 35), undated; 1; 00:10:21 (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889908)
        No. 2
      - Unknown (PT 42), undated; 1; 00:14:14 (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889916)
        Simon 38 et 19; discours [?] sueda
      - 'So nobody is' for Henri Chopin (PT 62), undated; 1; 00:08:18 (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889924)
      - Christmas Music ? (PT 63), undated; 1; 00:24:07 (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889932)
      - Concerto Corale (PT 64), 1957; 1; 00:21:39; The program is distorted at times. (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889940)
        Iº farte; Villa Zingoue - Concerto musiche corale; 7 1/2 (19 cm/s)
      - Unknown. "Anthologie école canadienne" (PT 40), undated; 1; 00:45:44; The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889957)
      - Unknown (PT 173), undated; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104507125)
      - Unknown (PT 174), undated; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104507117)
        Most of this audiotape reel is a music mix.
      - Unknown (PT 8), undated; 1; 00:23:49; An empty reel is also included. (Box 48, Item barcode 39002104507273)
      - Chopin, Henri? "Disque igloo" (PT 26), undated; 1; 00:36:09 (Box 51, Item barcode 39002104506218)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Les 9 saintes phonies (PT 27), undated; 1; 00:40:39; Audio can be heard only on the left channel at the beginning and end of the program. (Box 51, Item barcode 39002104506192)
      - Théatre en Direct (PT 28), 1988 November 26; 1; 01:02:35; Clicks and pops can be heard on the tape. (Box 51, Item barcode 39002104506184)
      - Chopin, Henri. Danse des vocemes (PT 29), 1991; 1; 00:18:11 (Box 51, Item barcode 39002104506200)
      - Unknown (no PT number given), undated; 1; 00:16:11 (Box 51, Item barcode 39002104506226)
        dynamic integral tracks
      - Unknown. Fragment de pluralité (PT 206), undated; 1; 00:07:00 (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889312)
      - Unknown. (no PT number given), undated; 1; The audiotape reel is blank. It has not been digitized. (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104507182)
      - Vree, F. / De Vree, P. "Apollinaire Vers in het gehoor" (PT 89), 1968 November 15; 1; 00:22:45 (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889346)
        19 cm/sec., stereo
        1. April am Rhein
        2. Kleine Carol
        3. Rhitmy's kind
        4. Riviera
        5. Kinorama (stereo)
        6. E[m] roos
        7. Hetlevenis en B[accomov] (stereo)
        8. Exodus (stereo)
        9. Organon (stereo) (Toeguild Le Travaill[ur[
      - Vree, F. "Appolinaire" (PT 90), undated; 1; 00:25:08; Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889965)
        1) aris le nº 480 (eno.) sons le font Jusqú au 537 (eno.) "je demenre"; 2) apris le nº 635 (eno.) "je l[?] adore tontes...Jusqú au nº 659 (eno.) "si nerveuse" c'est marqué pas [?] collant chaque jois
      - Vree, Paul de. Untitled (PT 139), undated; 1; 00:04:45 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109889700)
      - Wendt, Larry. "Calibration tone..." (PT 50), undated; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104507091)
      - Wendt, Larry. "What is Man?" (PT 51), 1981; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104507109)
        7 1/2 ips, 1/2 track
      - Wendt, Larry. "The wonders of dental floss" (PT 132), 1978; 1; 00:09:31 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109889692)
      - Commercially released reel-to-reel tapes (15 reels)
        - Hausmann, Raoul. RLQS Varie En 3 Cascades, 1966-05-25-1966-05-26; 1; 00:25:17; Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109889726)
        - Nebel, Otto. UNFEIG, 1970-04-08; 1; 00:34:05; Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109889767)
        - Heissenbüttel, Helmut. spicht TEXTE (A), undated; 1; 01:06:09 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109889775)
        - Amirkhanian, Charles. 5 Text-Sound-Pieces, 1975; 1; 00:30:56 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002104503041)
        - Cage, John. John Cage Speaks Mureau, 1972 October 3; 1; 01:07:48 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002104503058)
        - Giorno, John. Balling Buddha, 1975; 1; 01:01:58; The program is distoreted at times. (Box 53, Item barcode 39002104503066)
        - Gyson, Brion. The Brion Gyson Show: Where is That Word?, 1975; 1; 00:30:11 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002104503074)
        - Einhorn, Nicolaus. Arbeiten, 1973; 1; 00:16:26 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002104503082)
        - Giorno, John. Johnny Guitar, 1975; 1; 00:39:50 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002104503090)
        - Chopin, Henri. Voyage, 1971 August-September; 1; 00:15:51 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002104503108)
        - Rühm, Gerhard. Litaneien, 1975; 1; 00:40:38 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002104503116)
        - MacLow, Jackson. The Black Tarantula, 1975; 1; 00:34:01 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002104503124)
        - Jandl, Ernst. 13 Radiophone Texte, undated; 1; 00:28:32 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002104503132)
        - Heidsieck, Bernard. Carrefour, 1973; 1; 00:57:49; Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 53, Item barcode 39002104503140)
        - Hausmann, Raoul. Phonemes, 1970; 1; 00:15:35; The program is distorted at times. There is a high amount of hiss on the tape. (Box 53, Item barcode 39002104503157)
    - 10" and 12" vinyl sound discs
      Boxes 54-60 (sound recordings): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Music for Tape / Band - Musik, circa 1971 (Box 54 (Record Album Storage))
      - AHAHAHA8 / 8HAHAHAH, 1970 (Box 54 (Record Album Storage))
      - Text-sound Festivals-10 years, 1977 (Box 54 (Record Album Storage))
      - Smack My Crack, 1987 (Box 54 (Record Album Storage))
      - Text-sound-compositions 1, 1968 (Box 54 (Record Album Storage))
      - Text-sound-compositions 2, 1968 (Box 54 (Record Album Storage))
      - Text-sound-compositions 3, 1969 (Box 54 (Record Album Storage))
      - Text-sound-compositions 4, 1969 (Box 54 (Record Album Storage))
      - Text-sound-compositions 6, 1970 (Box 54 (Record Album Storage))
      - Text-sound-compositions 7, 1970 (Box 54 (Record Album Storage))
      - Festival d'ln(ter)ventions 2, 1985 (Box 54 (Record Album Storage))
      - sound texts, 1970 (Box 54 (Record Album Storage))
      - 10+2:12 American Text Sound Pieces, 1974 (Box 54 (Record Album Storage))
      - The Nova Convention, 1979 (Box 54 (Record Album Storage))
      - Futura. Poesia Sonora, 1978 (Box 55 (Record Album Storage))
      - Vooxing Poooêtre, 1982 (Box 55 (Record Album Storage))
      - poesia sonora, 1975 (Box 55 (Record Album Storage))
      - Canada - Italy, 1987 (Box 55 (Record Album Storage))
      - California - Italia, 1990 (Box 55 (Record Album Storage))
      - New Machine Voice, 1990 (Box 55 (Record Album Storage))
      - Ungheria + Italia, 1992 (Box 55 (Record Album Storage))
      - 5 september 1982. A tribute to John Cage, 1983 (Box 55 (Record Album Storage))
      - Ay-o & Emmett Williams. Fluxus Song #2 / Meditations 1, 2000 (Box 55 (Record Album Storage))
      - Barras, Vincent & Demierre, Jacques. Au homard, 1987-1988 (Box 55 (Record Album Storage))
      - Barrière, Françoise & Clozier, Christian. Oeuvres réalisées, undated (Box 55 (Record Album Storage))
      - Barrière, Françoise & Clozier, Christian. cordes-ci, cordes-ça / la discordatura, 1972 (Box 56 (Record Album Storage))
      - Bekaert, Jacques. Igloo, 1981 (Box 56 (Record Album Storage))
      - Birth Refusal / Cassis Comuta. Untitled, 2007 (Box 56 (Record Album Storage))
      - Blomdahl, Karl-Binger & Johnson, Bengt Emil. Dokumenation 2, undated (Box 56 (Record Album Storage))
      - Bodin, Lars-Gunnar & Johnson, Bengt Emil. Semikolon, undated (Box 56 (Record Album Storage))
      - Burroughs, William S. & Giorno, John. A D'Arc Press Selection, 1975 (Box 56 (Record Album Storage))
      - The Cascet Sinkers. Untitled, 2005 (Box 56 (Record Album Storage))
      - Chopin, Henri. Les Mirifiques Tundras & Compagnie, 1997 (Box 56 (Record Album Storage))
      - Chopin, Henri. Cantata for Two Farts & Co., 1997 (Box 56 (Record Album Storage))
      - Chopin, Henri. Poésie sonore, 1983 (Box 56 (Record Album Storage))
      - Chopin, Henri. Audiopoems, 1971 (Box 56 (Record Album Storage))
      - Chopin, Henri. La plaine des respirs, 2007 (Box 56 (Record Album Storage))
      - Chopin, Henri. Audiopoems, 1971 (Box 56 (Record Album Storage))
      - Chopin, Henri. Pêche de nuit, 1996 (Box 57 (Record Album Storage))
      - Clozier, Christian & Lejeune, Jacques. Oeuvres réalisées, undated (Box 57 (Record Album Storage))
      - Cobbing, Bob & Jandl, Ernst. Sound poems / Sprechgedichte, undated (Box 57 (Record Album Storage))
      - Corner, Philip. Piano Work, 2000 (Box 57 (Record Album Storage))
      - Corner, Philip. Word - Voices, 1997 (Box 57 (Record Album Storage))
      - Corner, Philip. 2 Works for Gamelan Ensemble, 1983 (Box 57 (Record Album Storage))
      - De Dyster, Edmond. Selectie 01, 2006 (Box 57 (Record Album Storage))
      - De Vree, Paul. Toute prédication, 1982 (Box 57 (Record Album Storage))
      - Eichenberger, Markus. Atemwerke, 1987 (Box 57 (Record Album Storage))
      - Figueras / Toop / Burwell. Cholagogues, 1977 (Box 57 (Record Album Storage))
      - Filliou, Robert. Greetings from 'L' we are all green, 2000 (Box 57 (Record Album Storage))
      - Flatus Vocis Trio. Grosso Modo, circa 1990 (Box 57 (Record Album Storage))
      - Giorno, John & Waldman, Anne. A Kulchur Selection, 1977 (Box 57 (Record Album Storage))
      - Guillou, Jean. Visions cosmiques, undated (Box 57 (Record Album Storage))
      - Gysin, Brion. Poems of Poems, 1997 (Box 57 (Record Album Storage))
      - Hanson, Sten. The Sonosopher Retrospective, 1998 (Box 57 (Record Album Storage))
      - Hanson, Sten. Text-sound compositions, 1978 (Box 57 (Record Album Storage))
      - Heidsieck, Bernard & Janicot, Françoise. Encoconnage, 1974 (Box 57 (Record Album Storage))
      - Heidsieck, Bernard. Canal Street, 1986 (Box 58 (Record Album Storage))
      - Heidsieck, Bernard. P puissance B, 1983 (Box 58 (Record Album Storage))
      - Henry, Pierre. La noire à soixante, circa 1968 (Box 58 (Record Album Storage))
      - Hodell, Åke. 220 Volt Buddha, 1988 (Box 58 (Record Album Storage))
      - Hodell, Åke. Spirit of ecstasy / The way to Nepal, 1980 (Box 58 (Record Album Storage))
      - Kaprow, Allan. Courtesy, 2000 (Box 58 (Record Album Storage))
      - Kelley / Neilson. Graveside doles, 2006 (Box 58 (Record Album Storage))
      - Kosugi / Tudor. Music for Merce Cunningham, 1988 (Box 58 (Record Album Storage))
      - Lied Music vs. Boy-Band Tax Retuns. Untitled, 2006 (Box 58 (Record Album Storage))
      - Lieutenant Caramel. La boîte de pandore / carnet de chasse, 1986 (Box 58 (Record Album Storage))
      - Lockwood, Anna. Glass World of Anna Lockwood, 1970 (Box 58 (Record Album Storage))
      - Logos Duo. Improvisation - Composition, 1983 (Box 58 (Record Album Storage))
      - Mattioli, Giorgio. Inisfera, 1985 (Box 58 (Record Album Storage))
      - Miccini, Eugenio. Concerti di poesia, 1983 (Box 58 (Record Album Storage))
      - Minarelli, Enzo. The sound side of poetry, 1991 (Box 59 (Record Album Storage))
      - Morgon-Fisher (ed.). Miniatures, 1980 (Box 59 (Record Album Storage))
      - One World Poetry. Live from Amsterdam, 1981 (Box 59 (Record Album Storage))
      - Penderecki, Krzysztof. Kosmogonia, undated (Box 59 (Record Album Storage))
      - Petite Compagnie, La. Corpus, 1975 (Box 59 (Record Album Storage))
      - Phillips, Tom. Words and Music LXXIV, 1975 (Box 59 (Record Album Storage))
      - Pistolteatern. Tre från Pistolteatern, 1966 (Box 59 (Record Album Storage))
      - poetry out loud. number nine, 1975 (Box 59 (Record Album Storage))
      - Regild, Carsten. Voice of the wolf, 1975 (Box 59 (Record Album Storage))
      - Ricci, Anna (mezzosoprano). Interpreta obras de Andrés Lewin-Richter, undated (Box 59 (Record Album Storage))
      - Sarenco. Armaniana, 1982 (Box 59 (Record Album Storage))
      - Sarenco & Franco Verdi. Sanremando, 1982 (Box 59 (Record Album Storage))
      - Sarenco & Franco Verdi. A.I.P.S. Ensemble "San Remando", 1979 (Box 59 (Record Album Storage))
      - Schoenberg, Arnold. Pierrot Lunaire, Op. 21, 1978 (Box 59 (Record Album Storage))
      - Schwitters, Kurt. Ursonate, 1986 (Box 59 (Record Album Storage))
      - Sparnaay / Goethals / De Meester. Untitled, 1975 (Box 59 (Record Album Storage))
      - Steen, Jos. Electricity!!!, 2007 (Box 59 (Record Album Storage))
      - Szymanowski, Karol. Wszystkie utwory fortepianowe Andrzej Stefański, 1983 (Box 60 (Record Album Storage))
      - The Dial-A-Poem Poets. Totally Corrupt, 1976 (Box 60 (Record Album Storage))
      - The Dial-A-Poem Poets. At this point, with the war...., 1972 (Box 60 (Record Album Storage))
      - The Loop Orchestra. Suspense, 1990 (Box 60 (Record Album Storage))
      - Thielemans, Eric. A Snare is a Bell, 2007 (Box 60 (Record Album Storage))
      - Tyfus, Dennis. 0032 (0) 3 2934834, 2007 (Box 60 (Record Album Storage))
      - Van Rymenant, John. Memory stop, 1982 (Box 60 (Record Album Storage))
      - Verdi, Franco. Cut up, 1982 (Box 60 (Record Album Storage))
      - X04. Lost signals, 2007 (Box 60 (Record Album Storage))
      - Unidentified, undated (Box 60 (Record Album Storage))
    - 7" vinyl sound discs
      Boxes 61-62 (sound recordings): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - 3 vi tre. Minarelli ed. numero 2, 1983 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - 3 vi tre. Minarelli ed. numero 5: polipoesia, 1985 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - 3 vi tre. Minarelli ed. numero 7: l.s.d. & minarelli, 1986 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - 3 vi tre. Minarelli ed. numero 1, 1983 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - 3 vi tre. Minarelli ed. numero 3: amirkhanian, 1983 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - 3 vi tre. Minarelli ed. numero 4: Ilse & Pierre Parnier, 1984 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Agam, Yaacov. Tableau Tactile Sonore, undated (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Alkema, Tjeerd. Plafond / Sol, 1980 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Bory / Muller. La fabrication de crepuscule, 1985 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Chopin / Heidsieck. Stereo Headphones Record Number One, 1980 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Chopin, Henri. Alphabet et Glotte (1987), 1999 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Chopin, Henri. Petit livre des riches heures signistes et sonores, 1986 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Chopin, Henri. Pêche de nuit, 1996 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Dufrêne (ed.) L'Autonomatopek 1, 1972 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Epidemia. Bacterial voice, 1980 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Etant Donnes. El Carro, 1993 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Etant Donnes. Plutot l'exil du cinq doré, 1983 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Fogliati / Loratotino. Poesia liquida / il liquimofono, 1968 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Gestalt. Die zerstört werden muss, undated (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Gysin, Brion. Junk, 1983 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Hains, Raymond. Saffa, 1971 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Hodell, Åke. Verbal hjärntvätt, 1965 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Horizontal Vertical Band. Pelican Dance / Bugle Tune, 1980 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Hudak, John. Natura, 1995 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Jandl, Ernst. Laut und Luise, 1968 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Jandl, Ernst. hosi + anna, 1971 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Jandl, Ernst. Der künstliche Baum, undated (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Mac Low, Jackson. 1st Milarepa Gatha, 1976 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Macromassa. Darlia Microtonica, 1978 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Mallander, J.O. Decompositions, 1970 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Moineau, Jean-Claude. Manuel de conversation, undated (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Nannucci, Maurizio. Parole 1976, 1979 (Box 62 (Record Album Storage))
      - Nannucci, Maurizio. Parole/mots/words/wörter, 1979 (Box 62 (Record Album Storage))
      - Numminen, M.A. The World is / In order to, undated (Box 62 (Record Album Storage))
      - Pernes, Thomas. Zur Eröffnung, 1986 (Box 62 (Record Album Storage))
      - Reuterswärd, Carl Frederik. Hållertal & Tandförtunga, undated (Box 62 (Record Album Storage))
      - Schalss, Gerda. vogelsang / sonneborn, 1991 (Box 62 (Record Album Storage))
      - Shrewsbury Pumping Station. The Music of Machiner: Volume One, 1968 (Box 62 (Record Album Storage))
      - Stern, Anatol. Kraj. Wieś i miasto, undated (Box 62 (Record Album Storage))
      - Stock, Hausen und Walkman. Ventilating deer, 1997 (Box 62 (Record Album Storage))
      - Stock, Hausen und Walkman. Buy me / Sue me, 1997 (Box 62 (Record Album Storage))
    - Audiocassettes, commercially released and non-commercial
      Boxes 63-71 and 80 (sound recordings): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Baobab. "L'in / Canto del verso" (1 of 4 audiocassettes), 1994 June; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002109975657)
        Includes I. Poesia Dello Spazio, II. La Voce in Sintesi, III. Sul Confine In/Verso (I Parte)
      - Baobab. "L'in / Canto del verso" (2 of 4 audiocassettes), 1994 June; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002093778539)
        Includes III. Sul Confine In/Verso (II Parte), IV. La Parola Cantata, V. Sull'in/Verso Confine
      - Baobab. "L'in / Canto del verso" (3 of 4 audiocassettes), 1994 June; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002109975665)
        Includes VI. In Media Stat Versus, VII. Versi in Jazz, VIII. Note D'Ironia, IX. La Voce al Cubo (I Parte)
      - Baobab. "L'in / Canto del verso" (4 of 4 audiocassettes), 1994 June; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002109975673)
        Includes IX. La Voce Al Cubo (II Parte), X. Montaggi Di/Versi, Documenti
      - Ars Nova. "Far out at Sea" (CAS 19), 1984 March 10; 1; 00:54:10 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502886)
        Far Out at Sea by Morrow, Borum, Andersen. Performance on Danmarks Radio by ARS Nova, directed by Bo Holten, spoken voice of mermaid Emily Fader, sung voice of mermaid Agnete Christiansen. Duration 1 hour, live from Nikolay Church, Copenhagen.
      - Chopin, Henri. "A -> K" (CAS 17), undated; 1; 01:37:20; A high amount of hum can be heard. The program was recorded at a very high level. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502894)
      - Chopin, Henri." K -> T" (CAS 3), undated; 1; 01:35:39; A high amount of buzz can be heard on the tape. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502902)
      - Chopin, Henri. "1983", 1; 00:50:47 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502910)
        Contents of the cassette are listed.
        Face 1/Face 2
        1. Symphonie en Rut Jambette, 1982: 5' 35"
        2. Trio d'Eté, (1), 1979: 12' 12"
        3. Voyage in California, (2), 1983: 9' 15"
        1. Sol air, 1961-1964: 9' 46"
        2. 2500, ou les Grenouilles d'Aristophane, ou la Fortune, (3), 1967: 4' 57"
        3. Nous n'avons pas voix au Chapitre, 1983: 3' 35"
        4. Jouissance des lèvres, 1983: 4' 37"
      - Chopin, Henri. "Audiopoems 1956-1980", undated; 1; 00:51:13 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502928)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Audiopoems 1956-1980", undated; 1; 00:51:21; This appears to be a duplicate. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502936)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le Corpsbis" (CAS 2), undated; 1; 00:52:20; Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502944)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le Voyage Labiovélaire" (CAS 4), undated; 1; 00:23:18 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502951)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Pirouttes" (CAS 1A), undated; 1; 01:09:23; There are recorded silences from 5:30-14:19 and 43:19-44:08. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502969)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Pirouttes" (CAS 1B), undated; 1; 00:05:34 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502977)